Bruce Jackson and Diane Christian collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound Recordings
  - Sub-subseries 2: Newport Folk Festival, 1964, July 23-26, 1964
    - 069 / 64 1E / NFF 2B - Thursday evening concert, July 23, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0069; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Madeleine - Cajun Band
      - La Robe a Josephine - Cajun Band
      - Handsome Molly - Doc Watson and company
      - Ruben's Train [Reuben's Train] - Doc Watson and company
    - 070 / 64 1E / NFF 3A - Thursday evening concert, July 23, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0070; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Windham - Sacred Harp Singers
      - Calvary - Sacred Harp Singers
      - Rocky Road - Sacred Harp Singers
      - intermission
      - Old Tar River - Georgia Sea Island Singers
      - Buzzard Lope - Georgia Sea Island Singers
    - 071 / 64 1E / NFF 3B - Thursday evening concert - Joe Patterson; Elizabeth Cotten; Moving Star Hall Singers, July 23, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0071; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - The Fox Chase - Joe Patterson
      - Dance Tune - Joe Patterson, with the Georgia Sea Island Singers
      - Casey Jones - Joe Patterson
      - Miss Lucy Was A Pretty Girl - Joe Patterson
      - Georgia Buck (banjo) - Elizabeth Cotten
      - Freight Train (guitar) - Elizabeth Cotten
      - Come On In the Ark - Moving Star Hall Singers
      - See God's Ark - Moving Star Hall Singers
      - Talks about John Henry - Mississippi John Hurt
    - 072 / 64 1E / NFF 4A - Thursday evening concert, July 23, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0072; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Ezekiel in the Valley - Moving Star Hall Singers
      - Spikedriver Blues [Spike Driver Blues] - Mississippi John Hurt
      - Frankie and Albert - Mississippi John Hurt
      - Oh My Lord - Doc Reese, Benjamin Reese, John Davis, Robert Pete Williams [worksong group] ([?] songs from Texas prison)
      - Rattler - Doc Reese, Benjamin Reese, John Davis, Robert Pete Williams
    - 073 / 64 1E / NFF 4B - Thursday evening concert, July 23, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0073; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Shake 'em on Down - Fred McDowell
      - What Do You Think About Jesus - Rev. Wilkins and the Georgia Sea Island Singers
      - When I Lay My Burden Down - Rev. Wilkins and the Georgia Sea Island Singers
      - Golden Vanity (Lonesome Sea) - Phipps Family
      - Lonesome Valley - Phipps Family
    - 074 / 64 1E / NFF 5A - Thursday evening concert, July 23, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0074; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Lonesome Valley - Phipps Family (continued)
      - All I Need - Fred and Annie McDowell
      - Sundown Blues - Robert Pete Williams
      - Two White Horses (See That My Grave Is Kept Clean) - Hobart Smith
      - Tap Dance Song - Jesse Fuller
    - 075 / 64 1E / NFF 5B - Thursday evening concert- Jesse Fuller; Square Dance Group; Sleepy John Estes; Stanley Brothers [Jug Band?], July 23, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0075; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - San Francisco Bay - Jesse Fuller
      - Square dance demonstration - Square dance group (Clayton McMichen, fiddle)
      - Drop Down Mama - Square dance group (fiddle - Clayton McMichen)
      - Stop That Thing - Sleepy John Estes
      - Careless Love - Sleepy John Estes
      - White Dove - Stanley Brothers
      - Hard Times - Stanley Brothers
    - 076 / 64 1E / NFF 6A - Thursday evening concert, July 23, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0076; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Hard Times - Stanley Brothers (continued)
      - Go Ahead and Have Your Way - Muddy Waters (with Otis Spann, identified as "Mr. Spann," on piano)
      - Sweet Little Girl - Muddy Waters (with Otis Spann, identified as "Mr. Spann," on piano)
      - Tiger in Your Tank - Muddy Waters (with Otis Spann, identified as "Mr. Spann," on piano)
      - Hootchie Cootchie Man - Muddy Waters (with Otis Spann, identified as "Mr. Spann," on piano)
      - Finale
      - Way Over in the Promised Land [performer(s) not identified]
    - 077 / 64 2E / NFF 6B - Thursday evening concert?; possibly the beginning of another event, July 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0077; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      The tape may have been recorded on two or more dates: the Kentucky Colonels were scheduled to perform on July 26, and Wong and Mahoe were scheduled either for July 23 or July 24
      - [two unidentified numbers] - Kentucky Colonels
        Instrumentals
      - Turkey in the Straw (variation) - Kentucky Colonels
      - Some breakdown [unidentified] - Kentucky Colonels
      - Turkey in the Straw (variation) - Kentucky Colonels
      - [two unidentified numbers] - Kentucky Colonels
      - Welcome [spoke word] - Theodore Bikel
      - The Woman on Horseback - Kaupena Wong [Ka'upena Wong] and Noelani Mahoe
      - The Roughriding Cowboy Song - Kaupena Wong [Ka'upena Wong] and Noelani Mahoe
    - 078 / 64 2W / NFF P.1 #1 - Singing styles workshop, July 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0078; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Great Day - Sacred Harp Singers
      - Arlington - Sacred Harp Singers
      - Daniel in the Lion's Den - Dewey Shepherd
      - Swing Low Sweet Chariot - Dewey Shepherd
      - What Do You Think About Jesus - Rev. Robert Wilkins; Fred and Annie McDowell
      - Do Lord Remember Me - Rev. Robert Wilkins; Fred and Annie McDowell
    - 079 / 64 2W / NFF P.1 #2 - Singing styles workshop, July 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0079; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Flames d'Enfer [Les Flames d'Enfer] - Cajun Band
      - Drunkard's Song - Cajun Band
      - Highway 61 Blues - Fred McDowell
      - Louise - Fred McDowell
      - Going Down South - Fred McDowell
      - Lonesome Journey - John Davis
      - Lonesome Valley - Almeda Riddle
      - Lonesome Journey - Georgia Sea Island Singers
    - 080 / 64 2W / NFF P.1 #3 - Singing styles workshop, July 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0080; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - You've Got to Walk This Lonesome Valley - Joan Baez, Mary Travers, and Peter Yarrow
      - The Unquiet Grave - Joan Baez
      - Pretty Polly - Ralph Stanley and the Stanley Brothers
      - Man of Constant Sorrow - Ralph Stanley and the Stanley Brothers
      - East Virginia - Ralph Stanley and the Stanley Brothers
      - Zebra Dun - Glenn Ohrlin
      - In Arkansas - Glenn Ohrlin
      - Little Will Green - Ollie Gilbert
      - The Gander - Seamus Ennis
    - 081 / 64 2W / NFF P.1 #4, July 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0081; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      On the tape box, a line is drawn through the last three titles, so they may not be on the recording.
      - Did the Rerm [?] Do Da Dee - Seamus Ennis
      - Were You At The Rock (in Gaelic) - Seamus Ennis
      - My Name is McCarthy - Seamus Ennis
      - House Carpenter - Almeda Riddle
      - Life is Like a Mountain Railway [Life is Like a Mountain Railroad] - Ollie Gilbert and Almeda Riddle
        Trail song
      - A Miner's Life - Mary Travers, Peter Yarrow, and Ronnie Gilbert
        Union song
      - Do Lord - John Davis with the Georgia Sea Island Singers, Joan Baez, etc.
      - This May Be the Last Time - John Davis with the Georgia Sea Island Singers, Joan Baez, etc.
    - 082 / 64 2W / NFF P.3 #1 - Autoharp workshop; Mike Seeger, MC, July 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0082; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Eller's Grave - Neriah Benfield
      - Coming Round the Mountain (autoharp and guitar) - Ken and Neriah Benfield
      - Sweet By and By (two autoharps) - Ken and Neriah Benfield
      - Shortnin' Bread - Ken Benfield
      - Holy Unto the Lord (two autoharps and guitar) - Phipps Family
      - When the World's On Fire - Phipps Family
      - I Anchored the Love Divine [Anchored in the Love Divine] - Phipps Family
      - Grandfather's Clock - Doc Watson
      - Breakdown - Doc Watson
    - 083 / 64 2W / NFF P.3 #2 - Autoharp and dulcimer workshop, July 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0083; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Two Soldiers - Mike Seeger
      - Victory Rag - Mike Seeger
      - Benfield Hoedown - Ken and Neriah Benfield
      - Evening in Paris - Ken Benfield
      - Way Down in the Country - Ken Benfield
      - It's A Gift to be Simple [Tis A Gift to be Simple] - Jean Ritchie
      - What'll We Do with the Baby-O - Jean Ritchie
    - 084 / 64 2W / NFF P.3 #3 - Autoharp and dulcimer workshop, July 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0084; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Barbra Allen - Jean Ritchie
      - Don't You Remember Molly - Frank Proffitt
      - Sweet Bye and Bye - Frank Proffitt
      - Groundhog - Frank Proffitt
      - Temperance Reel - Chet Parker
      - Irish Washerwoman - Chet Parker
      - MacNamara's Band - Chet Parker
      - Polka - Chet Parker
      - Spanish 2-Step [Spanish Two-Step] - Chet Parker
      - Swanee River - Elgin Hickock
      - Red River Valley - Elgin Hickock
    - 085 / 64 2W / NFF P.3 #4 - Autoharp and dulcimer workshop, July 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0085; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Darling Nelly Grey - Elgin Hickock
      - Waterbound - Mike Seeger
      - Pretty Saro - Jean and Edna Ritchie
      - Old Man Who Lived in the Woods - Jean and Edna Ritchie
      - Aunt Rhody - Jean and Edna Ritchie
      - Talk - Rev. Robert Wilkins
      - Freight Train - Libba Cotten [Elizabeth Cotten]
      - Oh, Babe, It Ain't No Lie - Libba Cotten [Elizabeth Cotten]
      - Bulldog Blues - Robert Pete Williams
    - 086 / 64 2W / NFF P.3 #5 - Guitar workshop, July 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0086; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Bull Dog Blues - Robert Pete Williams
      - Late Night Boogie - Robert Pete Williams
      - Railroad Bill - Hobart Smith
      - Graveyard Blues - Hobart Smith
      - Catfish Blues - Willie Doss
      - Hawaiian tune [1] - Noelani Mahoe
      - Hawaiian tune [2] - Noelani Mahoe
      - Spanish Fandango - Libba Cotten [Elizabeth Cotten]
      - Thank You Jesus - Rev. Robert Wilkins
      - Prodigal Son - Rev. Robert Wilkins
        Part; Jagger style
    - 088 / 64 2W / NFF P.3 #7 - Guitar workshop; Banjo workshop, July 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0088; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Guitar workshop
      - Memphis Blues - Clarence White and Doc Watson
      - Lonesome Road Blues - Clarence White and Doc Watson
        End of the guitar workshop
      - Banjo workshop
      - Send for My Fiddle and Send for My Bow - Elizabeth Cotten
      - Here, Rattler, Here - Elizabeth Cotten
      - Ruben's Train [Reuben's Train] - Frank Proffitt
      - Cluck Old Hen - Frank Proffitt
      - Bonnie James Campbell - Frank Proffitt
      - Cuckoo Bird - Hobart Smith
      - Banjo Breakdown - Hobart Smith
      - Poor Ellen Smith - Hobart Smith
      - Whitehouse Blues [White House Blues] - Arnold and Doc Watson
    - 089 / 64 2W / NFF P.1 #5 - Topical songs workshop, July 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0089; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Going 'Cross the Mountain - Frank Proffitt
      - Pretty Little Miss - Frank Proffitt
      - I'm A Girl of Constant Sorrow - Sarah Gunning
      - I Hate the Company Bosses - Sarah Gunning
      - The Job I Left Behind Me - Bill Thatcher
      - My Name is William Hollister - Bill Thatcher
    - 090 / 64 2W / NFF P.1 #6 - Topical songs workshop, July 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0090; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Yo Soy Negro - Soy Ton [?] Contento - Rodriguez Brothers
      - La Democracia Dondé Está - Rodriguez Brothers
      - I Am A Rambling Hero - Seamus Ennis
      - I'm in Trouble - Seamus Ennis
      - My Father's Maid - Seamus Ennis
      - Battle of New Orleans - Jimmie Driftwood
      - He Had A Long Chain On - Jimmie Driftwood
      - Father's Grave - Len Chandler
    - 091 / 64 2W / NFF P.1 #7 - Topical songs workshop, July 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0091; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - To Be A Man - Len Chandler (continued)
      - Taking Me Away From You Train - Len Chandler
      - Cement Octopus - Malvina Reynolds
      - It Isn't Nice - Malvina Reynolds
      - Are You Walking There For Me - Malvina Reynolds
      - We're the John Birch Society - Chad Mitchell Trio
      - Barry's Boys - Chad Mitchell Trio
    - 092 / 64 2W / NFF P.1 #8 - Topical songs workshop, July 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0092; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - I'm Still Standing on the Edge of Town - Tom Paxton
        Anti-automation
      - Read It in the Daily News - Tom Paxton
      - The High Sheriff of Hazard - Tom Paxton
        Kentucky; mining strike song
      - Davidson and Wilder Scabs (Davidson-Wilder Blues) - Hedy West
      - There's Anger in the Land - Hedy West
      - It Ain't Me Babe - Bob Dylan
      - Hey Mr. Tambourine Man - Bob Dylan
      - Iron Lady - Phil Ochs
    - 093 / 64 2W / NFF P.1 #9 - Topical songs workshop; Freedom workshop, July 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0093; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Topical songs workshop
      - I Ain't-A-Marching Anymore - Phil Ochs (continued)
      - Freedom workshop
      - This Little Light of Mine - Freedom Singers
      - Over My Head - Freedom Singers
      - You Better Leave Segregation Alone - Freedom Singers
      - Keep Your Eyes on the Prize - Freedom Singers
      - Ain't Gonna Let Nobody Turn Me Round - Freedom Singers
    - 094 / 64 2W / NFF P.3 #8 - Banjo workshop, July 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0094; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Georgia Buck - Doc and Arnold Watson
      - Good Old Cider - Doc Watson and Gaither Carlton
        Banjo and fiddle
      - Jimmie Sutton - Doc Watson and Gaither Carlton
        Two banjos
      - Ramblin' Hobo - Doc Watson
      - Westfork Girls - Phoebe Parsons
      - Little Birdie - Ralph Stanley
      - Shout Little Lulie [Shout Little Luly] - Ralph Stanley
      - Bound to Ride - Ralph Stanley
      - Old Black Joe - Paul Cadwell
      - Virginia Reel - Paul Cadwell
      - Georgia Camp Meeting - Paul Cadwell
      - Ragtime Episode - Paul Cadwell
      - Way Down Upon the Swanee [Swanee River; Old Folks At Home] - Paul Cadwell
    - 095 / 64 2W / NFF P.3 #9 - Banjo workshop- Mike Seeger; Ralph Stanley; Bill Keith; Kentucky Colonels, July 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0095; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Wild Bill Jones - Mike Seeger
      - Needle Case - Mike Seeger
      - Clinch Mountain Backstep - Ralph Stanley
      - Hard Time - Ralph Stanley
      - Little Maggie - Ralph Stanley
      - Talk - Bill Keith
      - Chicken Reel - Kentucky Colonels
      - Bill Cheatem [Bill Cheatham] - Kentucky Colonels
        Banjo and mandolin lead
      - Shady Grove - Kentucky Colonels
        Vocal and instruments
      - Medley: Turkey in the Straw, etc. - Kentucky Colonels, with Bill Keith on banjo
    - 096 / 64 2W / NFF P.3 #10 - Banjo workshop, July 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0096; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Old Hickory - Keith Siggins and Kentucky Colonels
      - Auld Lang Syne - Keith Siggins and Kentucky Colonels
      - Nola - Keith Siggins
      - Double Whammy - Kentucky Colonels (Ray / Bush)
    - 097 / 64 2W / NFF P.1 #10 - Freedom workshop, July 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0097; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Which Side Are You On - Freedom Singers, with Len Chandler
      - 99 1/2 Won't Do (Carlton Reese) - Freedom Singers
      - Go Tell It on the Mountain - Freedom Singers
      - I Got A Job (song by Carlton Reese) - Freedom Singers
      - I Will Overcome - Moving Star Hall Singers
      - Regular, Regular (Give Me the Gourd) - Georgia Sea Island Singers
      - Believe I Go To Rolling - Dock Reese
    - 098 / 64 2W / NFF P.1 #11 - Freedom workshop - Theo Bikel with Ronnie Gilbert; Barbara Dane; Freedom Singers with others, July 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0098; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Hinei Matov [Hinè Ma Tov] - Theo Bikel [Theodore Bikel] with Ronnie Gilbert
      - You Just Can't Make It By Yourself - Barbara Dane, with others
      - Oh, Freedom - Freedom Singers, with others
      - We Shall Overcome - Freedom Singers, with others
    - 099 / 64 2E / NFF reel 7A - Friday evening concert - Clayton McMichen and Frank Wakefield, July 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0099; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - The Woman on Horseback - Kaupena Wong [Ka'upena Wong] and Noelani Mahoe (drum and guitar)
      - The Roughriding Song - Kaupena Wong [Ka'upena Wong] and Noelani Mahoe (drum and guitar)
      - Woman Who Was in Love With Love - Kaupena Wong [Ka'upena Wong] and Noelani Mahoe (drum and guitar)
      - Famous Flowers of Hawaii - Kaupena Wong [Ka'upena Wong] and Noelani Mahoe (drum and guitar)
        Sung in English
      - Alabama Jubilee - Clayton McMichen and Frank Wakefield
      - Old Joe Clark - Clayton McMichen and Frank Wakefield
      - Over the Waves - Clayton McMichen and Frank Wakefield
        Waltz
      - St. Louis Blues - Clayton McMichen and Frank Wakefield
      - Boil the Cabbage Down - Clayton McMichen and Frank Wakefield
    - 100 / 64 2E / NFF reel 7B - Friday evening concert, July 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0100; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Amazing Grace - Fred and Annie McDowell
      - Going Down to Louisiana - Fred and Annie McDowell
      - Louise - Fred and Annie McDowell
      - If the River Was Whiskey - Fred and Annie McDowell
      - Greenbriar Boys - Fred Weiss - Union Grove Winner on bass; Frank Wakefield - mandolin
      - Leave Breaking Blues - Fred Weiss - Union Grove Winner on bass; Frank Wakefield - mandolin
      - Little Birdie - Fred Weiss - Union Grove Winner on bass; Frank Wakefield - mandolin
    - 101 / 64 2E / NFF reel - Friday evening concert - 8A Greenbriar Boys / Moving Star Hall Singers, July 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0101; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Little Birdie - Greenbriar Boys
      - At the End of a Lonely Day - Greenbriar Boys
      - Blues My Naughty Sweetie Gives to Me - Greenbriar Boys
      - Sleepy-Eyed John - Greenbriar Boys
      - Been in the Storm So Long - Moving Star Hall Singers
      - Sign My Name - Moving Star Hall Singers
      - Get On Board - Moving Star Hall Singers
      - Row Michael Row - Moving Star Hall Singers
    - 102 / 64 2E / NFF reel 8B - Friday evening concert / Chad Mitchell Trio, July 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0102; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - We're Going to Miss Ole Miss
      - Russian Song
      - Virgin Mary Had A Baby Boy
      - Wimoweh
      - We're Barry's Boys
      - Satire on the Nites of Xmas [Satire on the nights of Christmas]
    - 103 / 64 2E / NFF reel 9A - Friday evening concert, July 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0103; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Les Flames D'Enfer - Cajun Band [probably the Eunice Playboys]
      - La Valse du Musicien - Cajun Band [probably the Eunice Playboys]
      - The Bosco Stomp - Cajun Band [probably the Eunice Playboys]
      - Milk Cow Blues [?] - Sleepy John Estes
      - [unidentified] - Sleepy John Estes
    - 104 / 64 2E / NFF reel 9B - Friday evening concert, July 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0104; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Balling the Jack - Sleepy John Estes (continued)
      - I Been Well Gone - Sleepy John Estes
      - Doin' the Twist - Sleepy John Estes
      - Shout, Baby, Shout (alternate title: Jim Dandy) - Sleepy John Estes
      - I Ain't A-Marching Any More - Phil Ochs
      - The Power and the Glory - Phil Ochs
    - 105 / 64 2E / NFF reel 10A - Friday evening concert, July 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0105; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - I Ain't Marchin' Anymore - Phil Ochs (continued)
      - The Power and the Glory - Phil Ochs
      - Draft Dodger Ra - Phil Ochs
      - Links on the Chain - Phil Ochs
      - Talking Vietnam - Phil Ochs
        "Dedicated to McNamara and other liberals"
      - Freight Train - Libba Cotten [Elizabeth Cotten]
    - 106 / 64 2E / NFF reel 10B - Friday evening concert - Watson Family; Joan Baez, July 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0106; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - I'm Going Away - Libba Cotten [Elizabeth Cotten] (continued)
      - Study War No More (Down By the Riverside) - Libba Cotten [Elizabeth Cotton]
      - Lights in the Valley - Watson Family
      - The Beaumont Rag - Watson Family
      - I Heard My Mother Weepin' - Watson Family
      - Hey Miss Lisa Jane - Watson Family
      - There, But for Fortune - Joan Baez
    - 107 / 64 2E / NFF reel 11A - Friday evening concert, July 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0107; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - [unidentified] - Watson Family
        "Last Watson Family tune"
      - There But for Fortune - Joan Baez
      - Fair and Tender Ladies - Joan Baez
      - Black Veil [probably Long Black Veil] - Joan Baez
      - Birmingham Sunday - Joan Baez
      - T'adore - Joan Baez
      - Watch Out Joys - Joan Baez
      - Fennario - Joan Baez
    - 108 / 64 2E / NFF reel 11B - Friday evening concert, July 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0108; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Fennario - Joan Baez
      - Pilgrim of Sorrow - Joan Baez
      - All My Trials - Joan Baez
      - It Ain't Me, Babe - Joan Baez and Bob Dylan
      - We Shall Overcome - Joan Baez
    - 109 / 64 3W / NFF P.1 #12 - International songs workshop, July 25, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0109; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Rodriguez Brothers
      - Lucumi Elegua
      - Arara Rhythmic So[?]
      - Kaupena Wong [Ka'upena Wong] and Noelani Mahoe
      - Aia La O Pele
      - Ukeke
      - [?]lop
    - 110 / 64 3W / NFF P.1 #13 - International songs workshop, July 25, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0110; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Nose flute - Kaupena Wong [Ka'upena Wong] and Noelani Mahoe
      - Sushana-ea [?] - Kaupena Wong [Ka'upena Wong] and Noelani Mahoe
      - Madeleine - Cajun Brothers
      - Tedodo [?] - Cajun Brothers
      - Grinmumu [?] - Cajun Brothers
      - Believe - Hamza El Din
      - Peace - Hamza El Din
      - Kut Kut - Hamza El Din
    - 111 / 64 3W / NFF P.1 #14 - International songs workshop, July 25, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0111; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Performers: Sonia Malkine (French), Ron Eliran (Israeli).
    - 112 / 64 3W / NFF P.1 #15 - International songs workshop, July 25, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0112; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - As I Rode Out - Seamus Ennis
      - Lord Gregory - Seamus Ennis
      - Bald-Headed End of the Broom - Seamus Ennis
      - Tanganyika Song [Tanganyika] - Pete Seeger
      - Scottish Song - Pete Seeger
      - Hallow'd Be Thy Name - Joan Baez
    - 113 / 64 3W / NFF P.1 #16 - International songs workshop, July 25, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0113; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Let's Have a Bloody Good Cry - Joan Baez
      - Ole Mulherin' Da[?] - Joan Baez
      - Panavero [?] - Theo Bikel
      - Proshay [?] 0 Theo Bikel
    - 114 / 64 3W / NFF P.2 #1A - String bands, July 25, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0114; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Bonaparte's Retreat - Hobart Smith
      - Soldier's Joy - Hobart Smith
        With dancers
      - Sourwood Mountain - Phoebe Parsons, with son Roscoe
      - Don't My Baby Like Shortnin' Bread - Phoebe Parsons, with son Roscoe
      - Muskrat - Doc Watson and Gaither Carlton
      - Handsome Molly - Doc Watson and Gaither Carlton
      - Goin' Down the Road Feelin' Bad - Doc and Arnold Watson, and Gaither Carlton
      - Cripple Creek - Doc and Arnold Watson, and Gaither Carlton
    - 115 / 64 3W / NFF P.2 #1B - String bands, July 25, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0115; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Cripple Creek - Doc and Arnold Watson, with Gaither Carlton (continued)
      - Blue Ridge Mountain Blues - Doc and Arnold Watson, with Gaither Carlton and Merle Watson
      - Little Log Cabin by the Sea - Phipps Family
      - Climb the Last Mountain of Time - Phipps Family
      - Bring Back That Blue-Eyed Boy to Me - Phipps Family
      - Diamonds in the Rough - Phipps Family